http://www.cmfi.org/cmf-international-privacy-policy

Contact Us
Move vital ministry forward by giving where needed most.
Privacy Policy
CMF International (Christian Missionary Fellowship) is a 501(c)3 non-profit whose mission is to create dynamic, Christ-centered communities that transform the world. We are based in Indianapolis, Indiana, United States, and have personnel serving in many countries.
The basics of privacy and security
You do not need to register or supply any personal information to browse our website. We share your data only with our trusted vendors and service providers we hire to assist us in processing donations and sending communications.
By agreeing to this privacy policy, creating an account, making a donation, filling out a form, subscribing to our updates, communicating with us, or asking us to contact you, you understand that you are providing this information to us voluntarily and there is a legitimate reason for us to retain this information for the period required to fulfill these obligations.
This website utilizes appropriate levels of security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you provide. To protect your privacy, any collected information is encrypted during transmission to prevent unauthorized or unlawful access or processing. Our website is secure, encrypted with current SSL certificates. We do regular tests to ensure security. As a precaution, we do not store credit card information at CMF and that information cannot be accessed through our site.
As an added level of accountability, CMF belongs to the Evangelical Council for Financial Accountability, which monitors and accredits nonprofit Christian organizations.
Common ways you provide information to us
You subscribe to receive communication from us, provide us with information on a web form, comment on a blog, or otherwise correspond with us.
You provide information in the course of making a financial donation. Remember that we do not store credit card numbers!
You provide information when creating an online account or update or add information to your profile or preferences.
You complete an application or pre-application when pursuing serving with us on the mission field.
Information collected through cookies
Like many websites, we may use cookies in order to provide you with a more personalized web experience. It is necessary for us to store this small amount of information to deliver the website functionality you would expect.
A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that is downloaded onto your computer when you visit a website. Cookies can do a number of things, like remembering your preferences, recording what you have put in your cart, and remembering what pages you’ve visited.
We also use some cookies that do not collect personal information but that do help us collect anonymous information about how people use our website. We use Google Analytics for this purpose. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website usage by means of cookies. The data is collected anonymously, stored by Google, and used by us to create reports about our website usage. Google’s privacy policy is available at http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
Data collected when you share information on social media sites
When you share information with social media sites, those sites may give us automatic access to certain personal information retained by them about you (e.g. content viewed by you, content liked by you and information about the advertisements you have viewed or clicked). You control your personal information through the privacy settings you choose on social media sites. By associating an account managed by a social media site with your account and authorizing us to have access to this information, you agree that we can collect, use and retain the information provided by these social media sites in accordance with this privacy policy. We may also use plug-ins or other technologies from various social media sites. If you click on a link provided via a social media plug in, you are voluntarily establishing a connection with that respective social media site.
Ways we might use your personal data
To contact you and/or assess the application information you submitted to explore an opportunity to serve with CMF.
To respond to your inquiries when you submit feedback or questions.
To send updates and targeted marketing information about our ministry activities (stories, giving opportunities, news, etc.) if you consent to regularly receive such information. Any subscription is optional and free, and you may unsubscribe at any time.
To process donations, as requested and directed by the donor.
How you can exercise your data subject rights
If you would like to access, review, update, rectify, and delete any personal information we hold about you, or exercise any other data subject right available to you under the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you can email us. Our team will examine your request and respond to you as quickly as possible.
Changes to this privacy policy
We reserve the right to change this privacy notice at any time and will publish the most current version on our website. If a change meaningfully reduces your rights, we’ll notify people whose personal data we hold are affected. Your continued use of our website and services after any change to this privacy notice will constitute your acceptance of such changes.
How to contact us
If you have any issues with our privacy policy or if you feel your data has been used unfairly, then please contact us at missions@cmfi.org, call us at 317.578.2700 or send a letter to CMF International, PO Box 501020, Indianapolis, IN 46250.
Last updated on July 12, 2018.
Select LanguageArabicChinese (Simplified)DutchEnglishFrenchGermanItalianPortugueseRussianSpanish
Privacy Policy
CMF InternationalPO Box 501020, 5525 E. 82nd Street, Indianapolis, IN 46250317.578.2700 missions@cmfi.org
